(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
Ahoy!! キミたちみんなパイレーツ♡
Ahoy!! You're All Pirates♡
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To all visitors
演出の都合上、照明の明滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
受注生産グッズ 1
Made-to-order goods 1
受注生産グッズ 2
Made-to-order goods 2
受注生産グッズ 3
Made-to-order goods 3
受注生産グッズ 4
Made-to-order goods 4
Ahoy!
Sponsors
協賛
Sponsors 協賛
Sponsors
最近行ったのよ、カラオケ。
Recently, I went to karaoke.
なんさ、2時間で解散と思うじゃん？
I mean, you'd think it's over after two hours, right?
そっからなのよ。
But that's where it really starts.
いろんなことできるわけ。
You can do so many things now.
やばいぞ！
It's incredible!
PLAY! NEW (X).
X PARK
X PARK 最高！
X PARK is the best!
JOYSOUND X1
全国のアミューズメント施設にて 宝鐘マリン 限定プライズが 順次展開中！
Houshou Marine limited prizes are now rolling out at amusement centers nationwide!
12/7(土)より順次展開 寝そべりぬいぐるみ -宝鐘マリン②-
Rolling out starting 12/7 (Sat): Nesoberi Plushie -Houshou Marine ②-
対象機に500円投入で、オリジナルショッパーを1枚プレゼント！
Insert 500 yen into eligible machines to receive one original shopper bag!
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
宝鐘マリン 1/7スケールフィギュア 予約受付中
Houshou Marine 1/7 Scale Figure - Now accepting pre-orders
宝鐘マリン プロデュース香水！
Houshou Marine Produced Perfume!
マリンタワーコラボ 2024.12.2(月)～12.29(日)
Marine Tower Collaboration: Dec 2, 2024 (Mon) – Dec 29, 2024 (Sun)
Houshou Marine 1st Live
Ahoy!! キミたちみんなパイレーツ♡
Ahoy!! You're All Pirates♡
Ahoy!! You're All Pirates!!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To all attendees
受注生産グッズ 1
Made-to-order goods 1
受注生産グッズ 2
Made-to-order goods 2
受注生産グッズ 3
Made-to-order goods 3
受注生産グッズ 4
Made-to-order goods 4
宝鐘マリン危機一髪
Houshou Marine Kiki Ippatsu
宝鐘マリン 1/7スケールフィギュア
Houshou Marine 1/7 Scale Figure
宝鐘マリン プロデュース 香水！
Houshou Marine Produced Perfume!
マリンタワーコラボ
Marine Tower Collaboration
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
Sponsors 協賛
Sponsors
Anideal
宝鐘海賊団船長、宝鐘マリン。
Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine.
宝鐘マリン プロデュース香水。
Houshou Marine produced perfume.
横にするとボトルシップ風に！
Turn it sideways for a bottled ship look!
特製ポストカード付き！！
Comes with a special postcard!!
宝鐘マリン プロデュース香水。
Houshou Marine produced perfume.
Anideal公式サイトにて好評受注中！
Now accepting orders on the Anideal official website!
宝鐘マリン × U-TREASURE
コラボジュエリーが発売決定！
Houshou Marine x U-TREASURE
collaboration jewelry is coming!
Attention
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
宝鐘マリン1stライブ 受注生産グッズ
Houshou Marine 1st Live: Made-to-order Goods
宝鐘マリン危機一発 予約受付中！
Houshou Marine Pop-up Pirate - Now accepting pre-orders!
宝鐘マリン 1/7スケールフィギュア 予約受付中
Houshou Marine 1/7 Scale Figure - Now accepting pre-orders
マリンタワーコラボ 開催決定！
Marine Tower collaboration confirmed!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
宝鐘マリン1stライブ「Ahoy!! キミたちみんなパイレーツ♡」
Houshou Marine 1st Live "Ahoy!! You're All Pirates♡"
あー、マリンです。
Ah, I'm Marine.
本物のマリンです。あほーい！
The real Marine. Ahoy!
わー！ありがとう。
Wow! Thank you.
さぁ、大事な話します。
Now, I have some important things to say.
本日は宝鐘マリン 1st ライブ「Ahoy!! キミたちみんなパイレーツ♡」にご来場いただきまして、
Thank you very much for coming today to Houshou Marine's 1st Live "Ahoy!! You're All Pirates♡."
誠にありがとうございます。
We truly appreciate it.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
開演に先立ちまして、お客様にご注意ならびにご案内申し上げます。
Prior to the start of the performance, we have some warnings and information for our guests.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, audio recording, and the use of recording equipment during the performance are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。
Smoking is prohibited inside the building.
喫煙はご遠慮くださいますようお願い申し上げます。
We kindly ask that you refrain from smoking.
万が一、体調に異変を感じる場合は、無理をせず係員へお申し出ください。
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please do not overexert yourself and inform a staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、肩車、
Mosh, dive, shoulder rides inside the venue,
ステージ上に物を投げ込む、ステージ上に上がる、
throwing objects onto the stage, climbing onto the stage,
故意に通路を塞ぐ、前に押し寄せる、
intentionally blocking aisles, rushing to the front,
周りのお客様のご迷惑となるような不自然なコール、奇声、
unnatural calls or screams that may disturb other guests,
公演の妨げとなる大きな音を鳴らすなどの行為、
acts such as making loud noises that interfere with the performance,
不自然なタイミングで両手を左右に激しく振る、腕を振り回す、
violently waving both hands left and right at unnatural times, swinging arms around,
上半身を反らすなどの過激な応援行為、過度なジャンプ行為など、
extreme cheering acts such as bending the upper body backwards, excessive jumping, etc.,
他のお客様のご迷惑になる、または公演を妨げる危険行為は
dangerous acts that disturb other guests or interfere with the performance
一切禁止です。
are strictly prohibited.
本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
For this performance, cameras for video distribution and photography will be inside the venue,
客席のお客様の様子が映り込む場合がございます。
and guests in the audience may be captured on film.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに
These videos and photos may be used
使用される可能性がございますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
for promotional purposes, so please be aware of this in advance.
それではまもなく開演いたします。お席についてお待ちください！
The performance will begin shortly. Please take your seats and wait!
祝 マリン 1st ライブ
Congratulations on Marine's 1st Live
Houshou Marine 1st Live "Ahoy!! You're All Pirates♡"
宝鐘マリン1stライブ「Ahoy!! キミたちみんなパイレーツ♡」
世界が壊れてゆく
The world is breaking down
泣き声が聞こえていた
I could hear crying voices
汚れた拳　痛むほど
Dirty fists, until they hurt
強く握った
I gripped them tight
当たり前に笑っていた昨日はどこにもない
The yesterday when we laughed as if it were natural is nowhere to be found
明日がどんな日になるのか誰も知らない
No one knows what kind of day tomorrow will be
正義にさえ捨てられた今日を
Today, even abandoned by justice
取り戻すこと誓う
I vow to take it back
振り上げろ　勇気の旗掲げて
Raise it up, hoist the flag of courage
旅立とう　嵐の海
Let's set sail into the stormy sea
立ち上がれ　幸せは願えば
Rise up, if you wish for happiness
手に入るほど安くはない
It's not cheap enough to just be handed to you
守るために戦うなら海賊と
If you fight to protect, then a pirate
なればいい
you should become
キミたち！船長のライブ来てくれてありがとう！
Everyone! Thank you for coming to Senchou's live!
アリーナ！配信のみんな！
Arena! Everyone watching the stream!
全速前進！いきますよ！
Full speed ahead! Here we go!
幸せ簡単に手の中
Happiness easily in hand
消えてしまう
disappears
悲劇をただ見てることが
Just watching the tragedy
許せないなら
if you can't forgive
独り震えていた弱い自分消えはしない
The weak self that was trembling alone won't disappear
それでも決意胸に抱けばもう惑わない
But if I hold determination in my heart, I won't waver anymore
道半ばで倒れた友に
To the friend who fell halfway
託された言葉抱き
Clutching the words entrusted to me
振り上げろ...
Raise it up...
自由の旗掲げて 突き進め 大海原
Raise the flag of freedom and push forward into the vast ocean
燃え上がれ どんな荒波だろうとも
Blaze up, no matter how rough the waves are
揺らぐことなき 炎になれ
Become an unshakeable flame
光り上げ 勇気の旗掲げて
Shine bright, raise the flag of courage
旅立とう 嵐の海
And set sail into the stormy sea
立ち上がれ 幸せは願えば
Stand up, happiness is not so cheap
手に入るほど 安くない
That it can be obtained just by wishing
守るために 戦うなら
If you're going to fight to protect something
海賊になればいい
Then you should just become a pirate
声出して！
Let me hear your voices!
Yoh-ho-ho hara-he
Yoh-ho-ho I'm hungry
恐れずに ここで
Without fear, right here
赤き血の証を 立てろ
Make a vow of red blood
立ち上がれ
Stand up!
Yoh-ho-ho hara-he
Yoh-ho-ho I'm hungry
集まれば やがて
When we gather, eventually
未来（あした）を拓（ひら）く 海賊団だ
We're the pirate crew that paves the way to tomorrow
光り上げ
Shine bright!
出航ー！
Set sail!
魅惑を隠す箱
A box that hides enchantment
秘宝が香る危なげな
A dangerous thing that smells of treasure
Dangerous
Marine's smell
I'm Your Treasure Box
Ahoy!
ほら、そこにいる君たちに何て言ってあげるべきかな？
Hey, what should I say to you guys over there?
探してたのは船長？
Was it the Captain you were looking for?
うーん。あっ、そんなにかぶりついちゃダメだぞ。
Hmm. Ah, don't stare so intently.
かな？ お宝よりも魅力的なもの、見つけちゃった？
I wonder? Did you find something more attractive than treasure?
いいじゃなーい！
That's good!
砂糖まみれの その甘さ
That sweetness covered in sugar
極上の快感の秘宝
The treasure of supreme pleasure
それは私
That is me
艶が触れ漂う
The elegance touches and wafts
香りほど怖がらないで
Don't be as afraid as the scent suggests
開けてみて
Try opening it
(Laughing)
セクシー世界一 すっぴんピチピチ
World's sexiest, fresh-faced and youthful
無茶苦茶船長 捕まえたくない？
Don't you want to catch this reckless Captain?
欲しがった Treasure Maybe Destiny
The Treasure you wanted, Maybe Destiny
私の甘さが 欲しいんでしょ？
You want my sweetness, don't you?
Ah-hoy
秘宝の鍵を
The key to the treasure
優しく刺して
Gently insert it
DA-RA-DA-BU-I
宝庫の扉
The door to the treasury
マジで早く開けて
Seriously, open it quickly
Ahoy!
乱れたい あなたの手
I want to be disheveled by your hands
海図にこぼす 甘いため息の霧
A mist of sweet sighs spilled on the sea chart
純白のバラが
Before the pure white rose
萎れる前に
Withers away
ミリセカンドの過ち
A millisecond's mistake
七つの大海を
Over the seven seas
弄ぶマリンは罪な
Marine, who toys with them, is a sinful...
魔性のシャドウマリン
Demonic Shadow Marine
惑わされて何 探してんの？
What are you looking for, being led astray?
Now Please Grab Marine is Key
Open Up This Box
Open 痛いな
Open, it hurts
お願い してね
Please, do it
サヨナラだけは
Just don't say goodbye
開けろー！
Open up!
眠らぬ波のさすらい
Wandering on the sleepless waves
君たちもう 我慢できなくなった？
Have you guys become unable to hold back anymore?
Gather on the deck! ゼンブ・オン・ザ・デッキだ 準備はいいか？
Gather on the deck! All on the deck! Are you ready?
私の全てを手にいれて
Come and take all of me
Ah-hoy!
金銀財宝
Gold and silver treasure
確かめるでしょ？
You'll check it out, right?
しわしわになっちゃう
I'll get all wrinkled
誰か助けて！
Someone, help me!
マジで炎上しすぎ
Seriously, too much flaming
君たち、何考えてんの？
What are you guys thinking?
まさか、ムラっとかしちゃうの？
Don't tell me you're getting turned on?
だから今すぐぶち開けてよ！
So open it up right now!
マリン！マリン！
Marine! Marine!
私のもの、そう私のもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine
千の黄金、数百年の財宝
Thousands of gold, centuries of treasure
この船に眠る
Sleeping on this ship
古びた伝説は
The ancient legend is
呪われた幽霊船に
On a cursed ghost ship
続く夜の航路
The night route that continues
そこに富が残る
Wealth remains there
回答めいたガールのなら
If it's for an answer-like girl
いざ確かめるでしょ
Come, you'll find out, won't you?
無謀な作法、若き盗人よ
Reckless conduct, young thief
命を賭して怖がりを見せてやろう
I'll show you fear at the cost of your life
止まない雨の弾丸で
In a barrage of unceasing rain
愛おしいほど、この瞳を射抜く
So lovely, it pierces through these eyes
生命の炎、鮮やかな色彩
The flame of life, vivid colors
宝石なら
If it's a jewel
私のもの、そう私のもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine
バーチャル、命の証を
Virtual, the proof of life
あなたも求める全てを
Everything that you seek as well
輝きは全て錆びついて
The radiance has all rusted away
すべて泥にまみれるなら
If everything is covered in mud
泡沫とともに沈め
Sink along with the bubbles
黒い瞳が揺れる
The black eyes sway
極上の海賊の秘法
The ultimate pirate's secret treasure
かき集めて笑う
Gather it all and laugh
満月の金銀修行
Full moon's gold and silver training
七つの海の宝玉を組み
Combining the gems of the seven seas
猛る蟲ども
Raging beasts
孤高の美を狙う
Aiming for solitary beauty
愚かな神に思い知らす
Let the foolish god realize
凄まじき慈しみを
This tremendous affection
船に宿る、黒い魂の群れ
A flock of black souls dwelling on the ship
影の底で、忍び寄る絶望の渦 まるで
In the depths of shadows, a creeping vortex of despair, just like
二度と閉じぬ過去
A past that never closes
手放しちゃえば、諦めちゃえば
If you just let go, if you just give up
悪夢の中から抜け出せるのに、まだ縋る
You could escape from the nightmare, yet you still cling on
欲望さえ重いから
Because even desire is heavy
私のもの、そう私のもの
It's mine, yes, it's mine
自分自身を信じ込ませて縛りつけて
Making myself believe, binding myself
だって気づいた
Because I noticed
灯火の出口、永久の夜の怪奇
The exit of the light, the mystery of the eternal night
目を醒まして、あなたの悪夢から
Open your eyes and wake from your nightmare
連れ出す船で
On the ship that leads you out
出航して！
Set sail!
私のもの まだ私のもの
Mine, it's still mine.
熟の薔薇 朽ち果てたとしても
A mature rose, even if it withers away,
枯れない魂までは
until its undying soul...
魔法の呪文 永遠の美貌
A magic spell, eternal beauty.
そんな幻 願ったっていいでしょ
It's okay to wish for such an illusion, right?
手放せ 唾がついた家宝
Let go of the heirloom marked with spit.
ヨハネ・ザ・バッパー 向けて
Facing John the Bapper.
魅力を宿した船
A ship carrying charm,
希望だけ残していく
leaving only hope behind.
神様もいらないから
I don't even need God.
だじまり！
Starting!
まだまり！
Marine-ing!
愛してー！
Love me!
ムクロビ 死後のビート
Mukurobi, Afterlife Beat
ムクロビ・デ・ビッ！
Mukurobi de Bi!
死んじゃったらご愁傷 あの世でビッ！
Condolences if you die, beat in the afterlife!
でも存外楽しい 地獄でビッ！ビッ！ビッ！
But it's surprisingly fun, beat beat beat in hell!
もうクヨクヨしないで
Don't worry anymore.
ほら咲け咲け あやしてあげる
Look, bloom, bloom, I'll comfort you.
切り替えてこう Dance dance chu chu
Switch it up, dance dance chu chu.
ムクロダンス Dance dance chu chu
Skeleton dance, dance dance chu chu.
キスまで chu chu chu
Until the kiss, chu chu chu.
でもベッドは chu chu chu
But the bed is chu chu chu.
Dance dance chu chu
不安 Dance dance chu chu
Anxiety dance dance chu chu.
ビートに夢中 chu chu
Hooked on the beat, chu chu.
甘酸っぱい chu chu chu
Bittersweet chu chu chu.
踊れ踊れ死
Dance, dance, death.
君たちと踊れ踊れ
Dance, dance with you all.
無限にハッピーハッピーエブリバディ
Infinite happy happy everybody.
それでもいいじゃない
Isn't that just fine?
愛したい 誰からも愛されたいのって
I want to love, I want to be loved by everyone.
良くない？ 聞けない？
Is that not good? Can't I ask?
有り難たき幸せ 許してね
Grateful happiness, please forgive me.
契約わかったら返事
If you understand the contract, reply.
感動しました 泣けました
I was moved, I cried.
地獄最高！
Hell is the best!
ムクロビ 死後のビート
Mukurobi, Afterlife Beat
あちこち不便で寂しいですか？
Is it inconvenient and lonely everywhere?
マリンがいるでしょう！
Marine is here for you!
誰でもムクロビ
Anyone can be Mukurobi.
待って どうせこの世なんて
Wait, this world is just...
待って 皆どの一ツ
Wait, everyone, every single one...
ねえ待って 通り過ぎてくだけなのね
Hey wait, it's just passing by, isn't it?
待ってって言ったでしょう！
I told you to wait!
死んじゃってノリノリ
Dying and getting into the groove.
幽体離脱してサラッとマリンの本当の素敵な滾ったボディーは
Astral projecting and smoothly, Marine's truly wonderful, boiling body...
ぐったり尊死中
is drooping in 'death by cuteness'.
断然ホットな chu chu chu
By far, a hot chu chu chu.
ハートビートは家出 chu chu
The heartbeat has run away from home, chu chu.
昭和 かなり昭和
Shouwa, very Shouwa.
ビューティフル ビューティフル デッド
Beautiful, beautiful dead.
美しく バラをバラを
Beautifully, roses, roses...
平手打ちしてギュッとして
Slap and hug tight.
皆好き好き何もかも手に入れたいんで
Everyone loves it, I want to get everything.
地獄謳歌
Enjoying hell.
HOT HOT R.I.P.
ラッタッタ リホ 月と踊れや踊れ
Rat-ta-ta ri-ho, dance with the moon, dance.
さったほを張って歌えば風が吹く
Set sail and sing, the wind will blow.
ラッタッタ リホ 皆まだまだあがるんだった
Rat-ta-ta ri-ho, everyone was still going to rise.
大波小波をかき分けて 出航！
Pushing through the big and small waves, set sail!
ねえ もっともっと chu chu 遊び散らかして
Hey, more, more chu chu, play around.
羽ばたけそこがアンダーワンダーなんだわ
Spread your wings, that's what Under-Wonder is.
踊りもし致らばムクロに花束を
If we dance, a bouquet for the skeleton.
踊れ踊れ死
Dance, dance, death.
君たちと踊れ踊れ
Dance, dance with you all.
無限にハッピーハッピーエブリバディ
Infinite happy happy everybody.
それでもいいじゃない
Isn't that just fine?
皆好き好き好き好きを 超愛してる
Everyone, love love love love, I super love you!
ありえない不貞だらけの
Full of unthinkable slovenliness
呼吸して　許して　許して
Breathe, and forgive me, forgive me
サッサッサッと　ドクロになっても
Even if I quickly turn into a skull
終わらないカーニバル
A carnival that never ends
楽しすぎて　成仏しそう
It's so much fun, I feel like I'm passing on
涅槃者！
Nirvana!
キミたち！店長の声、呼び込めて！
Everyone! Call out for Captain's voice!
契約
Contract
成立
Established.
分かったら返事ね？
Answer me if you understand, okay?
アホイ！
Ahoy!
ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンです！
Hololive 3rd Gen, Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine here!
アホイ！
Ahoy!
二日目だー！
It's the second day!
やあ、キミたち。びっくりした？
Hey, guys. Were you surprised?
あの骸骨がさ、起き上がってびっくりしたでしょ？
You were surprised when those skeletons stood up, right?
あれキミたちだから。死んでたの。
Because that's you guys. You were dead.
よかった生き返ってくれて。
I'm glad you came back to life.
キミたち！二日目も船長についてこれるか！
Everyone! Can you keep up with Captain on the second day too?!
まだまだ盛り上がっていくぞー！
We're going to keep getting more hyped up!
はい、ここまでのね、曲はね…
Right, the songs up until now...
こないだセトリに思いなんか込めてないみたいなことちょっと透かしていっちゃったけど、ここは込めた。
I acted cool the other day saying I didn't put much thought into the setlist, but I did for this part.
ここ籠もってます。
There's a lot of thought in here.
マリンのね、あの何ですか、マリ箱…マリン出航、出航して…
Marine, you know, the Maribox... Marine set sail, and...
マリ箱で「や、お宝」と思ったら閉じ込められて死んだみたいな感じの…
I thought "Oh, treasure!" in the Maribox, but then I got locked in and died...
悲しくなんないでね、生きてます。
Don't get sad, I'm alive.
で、そっから生き返るみたいなね、感じのストーリー仕立てになりました！
And from there, it's like I'm coming back to life—it's become a story-driven performance!
ところでこの衣装さ、昨日披露したときとはどこか違うんだけど、どこでしょうか？
By the way, this outfit is a bit different from when I debuted it yesterday. Can you tell where?
袖！そう、袖！
The sleeves! Yes, the sleeves!
袖です！
It's the sleeves!
あとね、気づいた？
And did you notice?
ここ、このステージ、船なんです！
Here, this stage—it's a ship!
昨日はね、全貌見せないようにしてたんだけどね…
Yesterday, I was trying not to show the whole thing...
最後にバーンって出たと思うんだけど、これが船。
but I think it came out with a bang at the end. This is the ship.
これ今日ね、レンタル船なんで今日が終わったら解体です。
This is a rental ship, so it'll be dismantled after today.
キミたち、キミたち、嬉しいや！
Everyone, everyone, I'm so happy!
そうだ、思い出した。
Oh right, I remembered.
行くよ！
Here I go!
分かる？マリンのギターテクニックくらい…
Can you tell? My guitar technique is...
行くよ！
Here I go!
はい！
Yes!
どれどれ…
Let's see...
ちょっと待って、すみません、ちょっと音が、音が…
Wait a second, sorry, the sound is...
すみません、ちょっと待ってくださいね。
Sorry, please wait a moment.
マリンの今音トラブルが起こってます。
Marine is having some audio trouble right now.
マリンの耳の、耳のほうで。
In my ears, in my ears.
ちょっと待って、マジ、今、ちょっと待ってね。
Wait, seriously, just wait a sec.
ちょっと待ってね。
Just wait a sec.
今直してるから。
They're fixing it now.
こういうこともあります。
These things happen.
あ、でもキミたちの「うおー」ってのは聞こえる。ありがとうキミたち。
Oh, but I can hear you guys going "Whoa!" Thank you, everyone.
お、すごいすごいすごい。
Oh, wow, wow, wow.
キミたち、マリンのイヤモニが破壊されててもキミたちの声だけは聞こえるみたい。
Everyone, it seems like I can hear only your voices even if my in-ear monitors are broken.
あ！きた！
Ah! It's back!
やったー！
Yay!
いや、呆れた。すみません。
Man, I'm amazed. Sorry.
ごめんなさい、はしゃいじゃってすみません。
I'm sorry, I got too excited.
はしゃいではしゃいだら呆れました。
I got so excited that I'm amazed at myself.
待って。
Wait.
キミたち！
Everyone!
聞こえる！
I can hear!
直った！キミたち！
It's fixed! Everyone!
やった！
Yay!
いうわけでね、ちょっとすみません、なんかいろいろありましたが…
So, sorry about that, there were some things going on...
はい、ちょっとここで正気に戻って。
but let's get back to our senses here.
はい、まずは、いま韓国の映画館でライブビューイングを実施しているんですよ！
First of all, we're doing a live viewing in movie theaters in Korea right now!
アンニョンハセヨ！
Hello!
サランヘヨ！
Saranghaeyo!
はい。ここにも推しカメラがね、あるんで。
Yes. There's also a fav-cam here.
推しカメラ。あるんです、ここに。
A fav-cam. It's right here.
推しカメラ。あ、サランヘヨ。
Fav-cam. Ah, saranghaeyo.
うん。
Yep.
って感じで。
Just like that.
そして、配信で見てくれている君たち！
And you guys watching on the stream!
きゅんち！
Mwah!
あ、じゃあ推しカメラ、きゅんち。
Ah, then for the fav-cam, mwah!
配信の君たち、ちゅ、ちゅ。
You guys on the stream, mwah, mwah.
はい、ちゅしてと。
Okay, that's the kisses.
コメントも拾いますからね、ちゃんと今日も。 はい、安心してください。
I'll be reading comments today too. So please, be at ease.
ということでね、船長との航海を最後までしてほしいんだけど…
So, I want you to voyage with the Captain until the end, but...
YouTubeの無料枠は…
The free YouTube portion is...
はや！速い！判断が速い！
So fast! That was quick! The decision was quick!
えー、無料チラ見せはここまでになっちゃいます。
Um, the free sneak peek ends here.
そうだよ、えーだよね。YouTubeの君たち。
I know, right? It's "ehhh" time. You guys on YouTube.
チラ見せの無料の君たち。
You guys watching the free sneak peek.
チケット欲しいよね？ マリンと最後まで航海したいよね？ マリンと出航したいよね？
You want a ticket, right? You want to voyage with Marine until the end, right? You want to set sail with Marine, right?
概要欄にあります！
It's in the description box!
はい。なんで是非とも配信チケットを買って最後まで見てください！ お願いします！
So please, by all means, buy a streaming ticket and watch until the end! Please!
はい。
Okay.
では、次の曲行きましょう！
Now, let's go to the next song!
準備できてますか？
Are you ready?
さあ、キミたち！
Now, everyone!
盛り上がっていくぞ！
Let's get fired up!
無料パートは終了いたしました。 ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!